Why are you here?
Because I want to support the Somali community.
You want to support Somali community?
Yeah.
You're here every day.
I saw you every day here.
Yeah.
I thank you, brother.
You are the hero.
Hey, you're a hero, my brother.
Do you live in the neighborhood?
Yep, this is my boss.
This is my area.
I don't go into other people's neighborhoods and try to intimidate them.
I protect my people.
Are you giving out your name?
No, I'm okay with that.
Our neighborhood's showing up.
You guys had a lot of people out here, right?
At least 30 or more.
Yeah.
40 or 50.
That's pretty good for a quick turnout.
My name's Jack.
We're just trying to help pick up some release state tannies.
You know, they're left out in the cold.
Get up some supplies, get them home, whatever they need.
It's a cold day.
You could be on your couch watching a football game, your feet up.
Yeah.
That's exactly what I'd be doing, to be honest.
But who else is going to do it?
At this point, it's not the police.
We need the people.
They're not just going after criminals.
They're going door to door and they're targeting any black and brown person they can find.
And all of America is next.
Why do you, why do you, why are you out here instead of like being in your warm, cozy house?
Because there's a point where whites got to stand up and recognize that this is a white person problem.
And we need to represent our black and brown neighbors and disavow MAGA.
Yeah.
We need to put an end to this.